let questions = [
  {
    question: "Coffee is the ____ most traded commodity on earth.",
    options: ["first", "second", "third", "fourth"],
    correct: "second",
    reason:
      "It was the second. According to the Global Exchange, there are approximately 25 million farmers in over 50 countries involved in producing coffee. The number one commodity? Oil."
  },
  {
    question: "Where is the majority of coffee produced?",
    options: ["Brazil", "Columbia", "India", "Spain"],
    correct: "Brazil",
    reason:
      "Brazil produces 40% of the world's coffee, which is twice as much as 2nd and 3rd place holders, Colombia and Vietnam."
  },
  {
    question: "Coffee is actually a fruit.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correct: "True",
    reason:
      "Coffee beans as we know them are actually the pits of a cherry-like berry that are grown on bushes. Even though coffee is actually a seed, it's called a bean because of its resemblance to actual beans."
  },
  {
    question: "Where does the most expensive coffee come from?",
    options: [
      "Spain",
      "Cat Feces",
      "England",
      "Indian Farmlands"
    ],
    correct: "Cat Feces",
    reason:
      "And it comes from the feces of a Sumatran wild cat. The animal — called a Luwak — is unable to digest coffee beans. In the process of digesting the beans, they are fermented in the stomach. When the beans are excreted, they produce a smooth, chocolaty coffee."
  },
  {
    question: "How much cups of coffee does it take for it to be lethal?",
    options: ["5 cups", "10 cups", "20 cups", "> 100 cups."],
    correct: "> 100 cups.",
    reason:
      "However, you would need to drink over 100 cups to consume the lethal dose of caffeine."
  },
  {
    question: "Coffee stays warmer when you add cream.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correct: "True",
    reason:
      "Coffee with added cream cools about 20% slower than plain black coffee."
  },
  {
    question: "But when you add milk, it weakens the effects of caffeine.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correct: "True",
    reason:
      "Our bodies absorb coffee much slower when it has added fat milk content, which decreases the stimulants.."
  },
  {
    question: "Who invented instant coffee?",
    options: [
      "George Washington",
      "Michaèl Instàntè",
      "George Locke",
      "Richard Folger"
    ],
    correct: "George Washington",
    reason:
      "Not that Washington. Chemist George Constant Washington experimented with dried coffee before he created Red E Coffee — the first brand name instant coffee."
  },
  {
    question: "The average worker spends ____ a week on coffee.",
    options: ["$20", "$5", "$10", "$14"],
    correct: "$20",
    reason: "That totals nearly $1,100 annually."
  },
  {
    question: "What country brewed the largest cup of coffee?",
    options: ["Japan", "India", "England", "South Korea"],
    correct: "South Korea",
    reason:
      "It was over 3,700 gallons. The largest iced coffee was brewed in Las Vegas in 2010, and was 1,500 gallons — ice not included."
  }
];
